(Raj(voice off):)Hey, buddy, how's it going up there?
(Howard:)You don't have to shout, Raj.
(Howard:)It's not like I'm an astronaut
floating around in outer space.
(Howard:)Oh, wait, I am.
(Leonard:)So is it everything
you hoped it would be?
(Howard:)It's better.
Heh, I wake up every morning...
(Howard:)...and I just can't believe
I'm on this incredible adventure.
(Dimitri:)Hey, Froot Loops,
did you clean the space toilet?
(Howard:)Excuse me, I'm talking to my friends.
(Mike:)You know the rules,
new guy scrubs the toilet.
(Dimitri:)If you do good job,
next time we give you brush.
(Howard:)Funny.
(Howard:)We're always giving each other
a hard time up here.
(Howard:)It's kind of like being in a frat.
(Howard:)You know, joking, kidding around,
hurting feelings.